{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906345957","data":{"timestamp":" 946906345957"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906346501","data":{"timestamp":" 946906346501"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906347483","data":{"timestamp":" 946906347483"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" PALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906348057","data":{"timestamp":" 946906348057"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906348770","data":{"timestamp":" 946906348770"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906351391","data":{"timestamp":" 946906351391"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906351684","data":{"timestamp":" 946906351683"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906352357","data":{"timestamp":" 946906352357"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906352940","data":{"timestamp":" 946906352940"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906353784","data":{"timestamp":" 946906353784"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906354621","data":{"timestamp":" 946906354620"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906355067","data":{"timestamp":" 946906355066"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906355930","data":{"timestamp":" 946906355930"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906357278","data":{"timestamp":" 946906357277"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGAMIA"," userResponse":" NGAMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906358503","data":{"timestamp":" 946906358503"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906358520","data":{"timestamp":" 946906358520"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906358954","data":{"timestamp":" 946906358954"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906359528","data":{"timestamp":" 946906359528"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906362310","data":{"timestamp":" 946906362310"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWOA"," userResponse":" ALIMWOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906363092","data":{"timestamp":" 946906363092"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906364175","data":{"timestamp":" 946906364175"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906364807","data":{"timestamp":" 946906364807"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906367861","data":{"timestamp":" 946906367861"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906368145","data":{"timestamp":" 946906368145"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906368829","data":{"timestamp":" 946906368829"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906369072","data":{"timestamp":" 946906369072"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906369506","data":{"timestamp":" 946906369506"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906370171","data":{"timestamp":" 946906370170"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906370583","data":{"timestamp":" 946906370583"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906371567","data":{"timestamp":" 946906371567"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906372979","data":{"timestamp":" 946906372978"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906373493","data":{"timestamp":" 946906373493"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906374797","data":{"timestamp":" 946906374794"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFUNGUA"," userResponse":" ALIJIFUNGUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906375644","data":{"timestamp":" 946906375644"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906376603","data":{"timestamp":" 946906376603"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906379179","data":{"timestamp":" 946906379178"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMEWE"," userResponse":" MUMEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906380386","data":{"timestamp":" 946906380386"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906381294","data":{"timestamp":" 946906381293"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906381799","data":{"timestamp":" 946906381798"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906382884","data":{"timestamp":" 946906382883"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIVUNIA"," userResponse":" KUJIVUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906383588","data":{"timestamp":" 946906383588"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEWE"," userResponse":" MKEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906386112","data":{"timestamp":" 946906386112"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906386878","data":{"timestamp":" 946906386878"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906387081","data":{"timestamp":" 946906387081"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906387664","data":{"timestamp":" 946906387664"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906388524","data":{"timestamp":" 946906388523"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906389669","data":{"timestamp":" 946906389668"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906390225","data":{"timestamp":" 946906390225"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906391300","data":{"timestamp":" 946906391299"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWACHA"," userResponse":" ALIMWACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906391954","data":{"timestamp":" 946906391954"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906392821","data":{"timestamp":" 946906392820"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906393822","data":{"timestamp":" 946906393822"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" AKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906394504","data":{"timestamp":" 946906394504"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906395125","data":{"timestamp":" 946906395125"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906395599","data":{"timestamp":" 946906395599"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906396362","data":{"timestamp":" 946906396362"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKAMA"," userResponse":" KUKAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906396886","data":{"timestamp":" 946906396886"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906396898","data":{"timestamp":" 946906396898"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906399524","data":{"timestamp":" 946906399523"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906399787","data":{"timestamp":" 946906399787"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906400580","data":{"timestamp":" 946906400580"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAWAIDA"," userResponse":" KAWAIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906401224","data":{"timestamp":" 946906401224"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906402537","data":{"timestamp":" 946906402536"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWACHIA"," userResponse":" KUMWACHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906403280","data":{"timestamp":" 946906403280"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBUYU"," userResponse":" KIBUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906403474","data":{"timestamp":" 946906403473"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906403544","data":{"timestamp":" 946906403544"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" 7bffc327-a290-4b85-ab3f-5858edb4d1a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBUYU"," userResponse":" KIBUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906418253","data":{"timestamp":" 946906418253"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" ab20b218-4007-4af0-83be-d32b8cb3a274"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906418729","data":{"timestamp":" 946906418728"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" ab20b218-4007-4af0-83be-d32b8cb3a274"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906418800","data":{"timestamp":" 946906418800"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" ab20b218-4007-4af0-83be-d32b8cb3a274"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906530206","data":{"timestamp":" 946906530206"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" ab20b218-4007-4af0-83be-d32b8cb3a274"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906540912","data":{"timestamp":" 946906540912"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" fca0fa49-a90c-484d-8879-9ff09674b704"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-R-W"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906545707","data":{"timestamp":" 946906545707"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" fca0fa49-a90c-484d-8879-9ff09674b704"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-Y-U"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906549497","data":{"timestamp":" 946906549497"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" fca0fa49-a90c-484d-8879-9ff09674b704"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-Y-W"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906555177","data":{"timestamp":" 946906555177"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" fca0fa49-a90c-484d-8879-9ff09674b704"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-Y-W"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906990876","data":{"timestamp":" 946906990876"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_163137"," gameId":" fca0fa49-a90c-484d-8879-9ff09674b704"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-K-T"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}